Every time the rain no longer falls, and I
see the sky, I think the rain is falling.
Back to when I was a child.
Who could only cry?
Blindly chasing after him.
I fell far behind my only thought.
One day I will be stronger!
Bridery and gratitude.
Fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure.
But until I do, my voyage will not end.
No matter what's next, I'm
walking straight ahead.
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now!
Though time's all on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything
will take what I hope.
The voices inside me push
me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through,
no matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest storms of
all can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back?
So let's go,
there's nothing that can stop!
The times that are on our side
will never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hold dear away from me.
I know the future's there for us to see.
What is that?
It looks like a tunnel of flames!
Ever since you were little, you've
never listened to a word I said.
Have you?
Then you run off and do something crazy.
Like old times. Huh, Luffy?
Let's go!
That's Firefist Ace!
He's free!
Yee-haw!
You did a Straw Hat! Yeah!
You can suck it, baby!
He hasn't slowed down once
after all he's been through.
You can't stop this guy!
Your papa would be so proud!
See that?
He really did it!
That crazy little bastard saved Ace!
Of course he did.
After all, he's Luffy.
Keep your cool!
This isn't over yet!
Open fire as soon as they land! Sir!
Let's split up for now!
Don't let your guard down yet! Okay!
Wait, no!
Flame Commandment!
Fire!
They're strong! Be careful, men!
Can you still fight, Luffy?
Of course I can't!
Luffy! Ace!
Remember, Ace is a Logia Titan, so
he's going to be really tough to hit.
Never thought I'd need my
little brother to save me.
Guess I'll swallow my pride this time.
I owe you one, Luffy.
Thanks, but I sure couldn't have done
it if Whitebeard hadn't shown up.
You think we'll let you get away?
Consider this your
execution ground, pirates!
That's my little brother
you're trying to murder.
I'll have to ask you to stop
You're dead
This is fun and all, but the sooner
we leave this dump, the better, right?
They're a fine team, I dare say.
We're pulling out!
Clear a path!
We can't let them get away!
Firefly!
Fire it off!
This isn't over yet execute them both
I've got to admit, you've
gotten pretty tough, Luffy.
One of these days, I'll
be stronger than you.
All right, then I'll handle
things in the meantime.
What a pain.
All right, ice block.
Stand back, Luffy.
And now, Pheasant Beak!
Flame Mirror!
You're all right, sir?
This is the worst blunder of my life.
We have to rectify this.
Huh, just let him go.
It makes things more interesting.
I say
Cut the crap
Those guys went toe-to-toe
with an admiral.
What the hell are we supposed
to do pull yourselves together?
Admiral Sakazuki
They won't make it out of here alive.
Don't you worry
mr.
two i hope i could honor
your memory in my own humble
way anywho that's enough
heroism For a lifetime I'm
leaving what Splatoon is
this traitor from no hold on
he's a prisoner Impersonating
a guard no I was too slow
The enemy ship is coming
through On land somehow Don't
get close It's running on
the ground with his paddles
Wait, who's on board? I can't see.
It's Squared.
And it looks like he's
got his crew with him too.
Make a break for it, Pops!
We'll guard you.
We'll show those bastards the
pride of the spider world pirates!
God damn it!
What are you thinking?
Don't be an idiot squad!
You'll die!
Yeah, you got a death wish or something!
Yes.
Yes, of course.
After what I did to Pops,
this is the least I can do.
I can't hope to atone for my crime.
But if I don't die fighting here,
I know I'll never rest in peace.
I'm sorry for bringing you with me.
This should be my fight. What?
Are you kidding me?
We wanted to follow you.
Yeah, you're our captain,
to the bitter end.
If we all die here,
then that's our choice.
Let's not get sentimental here.
Lead the charge, captain.
Thank you.
Everyone else grab Ace
and make a run for it.
Saint Helmer's Fire!
Those fools.
Squared, no.
Oh, you think anyone's going to
be happy with a plan like this?
Hey, hurry up and get
these cuffs off of me!
What the hell?
Did we run into something?
But why, Pops?
You believe you've done me a favor?
You poor, selfish child!
Don't you know how cruel it is to
force a father to bury his own sons?
And show some humility!
You think I'm on my last legs
because of one measly poke?
It was settled long before I came here.
Everyone has to grow old and die someday.
Our
business is done.
Pull out now,
and I'll stay here to make sure I don't
lose any more of my boys to these bastards!
You're staying?
What do you mean?
Listen up, White Beard Pirates!
And listen well!
These are my final orders as your captain!
So you better follow them!
You're kidding, right?
That's the last thing we want to hear!
We're going back together! Yeah!
We can't go on without you!
We didn't save Ace to let our captain die!
Crossfire!
Let's go!
Even family must part ways now and then!
You must survive!
Return to the New World!
Continue your legacy without me!
No!
You can't die!
We can find another way!
Make no mistake!
I'm a relic of a bygone era!
Long have I sailed, but no ship
can carry me into the new age.
Now go and forge your own path!
There's no way we can leave you here.
Look, I know how you
feel, but it's an order.
Hulk, I know. What are you?
Don't look back, boys.
A new age is coming.
Oh, man, what a hole!
Hey, you don't even care
about treasure, you weirdo!
Come check it out.
There's plenty to go around, buddy.
Forget it, he's always like this. Huh?
What does that mean?
We wouldn't even have these
treasures without him!
Well, what are you looking for then?
Hey!
You listening, Newgate?
It's been a long journey, but a good one.
Let's finally put an end to this.
The rainforest's falling apart!
Somebody stop Whitebeard!
Damn!
At this rate, he's gonna
bring down the whole island!
We came here as a family!
We should leave as one, too!
Yeah!
Pops, come with us!
You mean to disobey your captain's order?
I told you fools to get away!
Alright!
This might be our only chance!
Hit Wipe here with all you've got!
I won't do it!
Hey, come on, we're better
off doing what Pops says.
Are you crazy?
Pops is our father!
I won't leave him here to die!
I know!
Don't be stupid!
Do you think any of us want
Dial Pops behind? Move!
Bickering about your own petty
feelings at a time like this,
that's the kind of stuff
Pops wouldn't stand for!
Can't you see that he's trying
to do what's best for us?
Sorry.
Everyone get back on the ships!
Hey, Ace!
Come on! Hurry it up!
We're about to take off!
Commander Marco, let's head back!
Pops.
He no longer has to worry
about saving firefish days.
Admiral, sir?
So long as his men can escape, he'll
sink Marineford and all of us with it.
He's prepared to die, I've no doubt.
Vice Admiral Garp, you okay?
Whitebeard thinks our era is over?
Yeah, the old man is probably right.
We still don't know what
happened to Whitebeard.
What about his allies?
Did he really sell them out or what?
Perfect.
How am I supposed to write
a story on the battle now?
What's wrong with their snails?
We don't go out all day!
Really?
That piece of crap is
still hiding in its shell?
Come on!
Get back out here, Mr. Snail.
We still need your help.
Captain Buggy's ready
to defeat Whitebeard.
Don't they realize what they're saying?
Yeah, Whitebeard's wounded, but
he's tearing down buildings.
Just look at the bastard.
Why'd I have to go and say I'd beat him?
These morons believe
anything you tell them.
It's their fault for feeding my ego.
I can't help it! Lure it out!
We gotta showcase Captain Buggy's
awesomeness for the entire world to see.
Bring it over here.
I'll just smash the shell open.
Yeah, one strong pound ought to do it.
Quit messing with the
paw thing, you fools.
The transponder snail came out on its own.
Come on,
we're starting the broadcast and make sure
you capture the moment
that I kill Whitebeard.
Hey, look. It's bad.
Transponder snail, go down a little.
Why, hello everybody!
Time for Captain Buggy!
This guy again?
Get to the sea! Now!
Hurry up and get on the ships!
We gotta make it back to
the new world and fast!
Don't let them get away!
Kill as many pirates as you can!
I'm the only pirate you
should be worrying about!
Commander Joseph!
He's in pretty bad shape,
but I think he can make it.
First, we got to get him
out of here to safety.
Everyone lift!
Ape 1-Eye! Get over here! On the double!
Hurry, straw boy!
It's time to make an exit!
On the double!
Ace, let's go!
The old guy made up his mind!
I know this is it.
Back off, you bastard!
Oh, my God.
The time for words has passed, my son.
But tell me one last thing.
Are you happy to have this
old fool as your father?
You got some fight left?
Look, I'm not gonna kill
you today, all right?
Don't fight it.
You're too valuable to
die in a place like this.
Run wild with us and our
flight will be yours!
And I will call you my son.
Of course, Dad!
Keep it up!
We're almost there!
Ace! Luffy!
Stay in front!
They're specifically targeting you two!
We cannot let the old man waste his life.
He will not fall in vain.
Farewell.
We've stolen the Navy ship. Hop aboard!
Do they really think they stand
a chance of escaping? How naive.
Admiral Sakazuki.
Move aside.
I'll handle this.
Never mind that just don't stop
running until you reach the ship.
As soon as they rescued Fire Fist
Ace they fled what a cowardly
crew just like their washed up
Captain he's trying to get you
riled up don't listen keep it
moving don't fall into his trap
You hear me yeah that old man huh
some captain he is it's not your
fault that's Just Whitebeard
a washed-up failure
failure
take
it back or else Ace no don't Just
keep moving he can say whatever
he wants let's go no one gets
away with mocking Pops Stop take
it back it's not an insult it's
the truth let me tell you a story
Your father conquered the Grand Line something
no other pirate has ever accomplished
After that he opened the door to the great
pirate era by sacrificing his own life.
I hate to say it being a Navy Admiral, but
he was King of the Pirates, no question.
Keeping all that in mind,
Whitebeard has failed.
His lack of ambition
meant he'd never be king
of anything but you simple-minded cronies.
Once he brainwashed enough of you into
doing his dirty work, he got lazy.
Every now and then you'll find someone
who paints him as a peacekeeper.
Start trouble here and Whitebeard
will come running, they say.
Empty post to keep
idiots like you fearful.
You call him hero when
he's nothing but a coward.
When Gold Roger was around,
Whitebeard always had second billing.
Yet even after Roger's death,
he couldn't become king.
So there it is, the tale of
your father's whipping boy,
the great failure Whitebeard.
Soon enough, he'll be dead,
and no one will remember him.
I can't help but feel sorry for the man,
and all you punks call him your pops.
Did you make this fake family to humor
him, or are you just as deluded? Shut it.
He sailed the seas for years,
couldn't amount to anything,
amassed an army of losers,
and in the end was even
stabbed by one of his own
sons who put more stock
in my word than his own.
And still, he'll die to protect that man.
Have you ever heard of
a more pathetic life?
That's enough leave him run you're wrong
there's nothing fake about
the family he gave us!
But I wouldn't expect a heartless
bastard like you to appreciate that
like I said he convinced You punk
you meant something to the world but
your kind doesn't deserve a home you
deserve The gallows you know it's
true you'll all die as failures and
Whitebeard's nothing but a lonely?
Whitebeard is the greatest pirate
who ever lived, you hear me?
You don't know anything about
the man who saved my life!
Get away from the base!
This is his era!
Don't you forget it!
Your pops will end up
the same as you, boy.
Dead and by my hand!
How?
Did he burn him?
Thanks to your Logia-type fruit,
you're not used to being hurt.
It's made you too cocky.
You may be made of fire, but my
magma burns even hotter than that.
Just like Whitebeard,
second-rate to the bitter end.
Yes!
Luffy, stay out of harm's way!
You're in no condition to battle!
He's his fever cart.
Gold Roger the King of the Pirates.
And Dragon the Revolutionary.
To think that the two of
you were adopted brothers.
All these years.
What a victory it'd be
to end both bloodlines.
Everyone else can escape.
The two of you are the
only targets I'm after.
Say goodbye? Die!
Please!
Luffy!